anytimecostumes.com 2003-04-08

# Party Lounge: <B><font color="FF6600">PRIVACY POLICY</font color></B>

Untitled Document

**SAFETY & PRIVACY**

S&S Party Lounge, Ltd. DBA AnytimeCostumes.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and using this information responsibly. Please read below for detailed information about our privacy policy. 

**HOW WE _DO NOT_ USE YOUR INFORMATION**   
Our site uses an order and registration form so you can request products or information. Contact information (email address, telephone number, address, etc.) from the order form will _NEVER_ be sold, rented, traded or even given away.  We respect your privacy.  The information you provide to us is STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL.    

**HOW WE _USE_ THIS INFORMATION**   
Contact information (email address, telephone number, address, etc.) from the order form is used to send your order and information about our company to you. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary. Financial information (credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, etc.) that is collected is used to bill you for products and services.

**IP ADDRESS & COOKIES**   
We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address also may be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information aids us in merchandising and in developing the design and layout of the site. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. They make it possible for us to recognize your browser when you visit. By doing this, we can personalize your return visits and save you time during checkout. In order to enjoy the benefits of being a registered user, your browser must be set to accept cookies. We may also collect and share information about the pages that you visit on our site, but this information is not personally identifiable

**HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS STORED**

This site uses a secure server (SSL) to encrypt all of your personal information. We use strong security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of your information once it is in our records. 

**YOUR AGREEMENT**   
By using our Web site or purchasing a product from us, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this privacy policy. We may from time to time update this policy. We will post any changes to our policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

**CONTACT US**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact: 

Customer Service

S&S Party Lounge, Ltd.  
http://www.anytimecostumes.com   
33 Comac Loop - Unit 2   
Ronkonkoma, NY 11779  
Phone: (631) 737-5008  
Email: customer.service@partylounge.com 

**QUALITY AND CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE**   
S&S Party Lounge, Ltd. is committed to quality customer experience. We are constantly reviewing your feedback to improve and enhance your shopping experience. You can tell us what you think by sending us an email or contacting our customer care department toll-free at 1-877-546-2757 Monday - Friday 9:30 AM - 6:00 PM EST.
